{
	"questions": [
	{
		"question": "What is the most popular artist/band of all time?",
		"optionA": "CJ",
		"optionB": "Queen",
		"optionC": "Elton John",
		"optionD": "Pink Floyd",
		"correctANS": "CJ"
		},
	{
		"question": "Which of the following decades is the most popular ever?",
		"optionA": "1990s",
		"optionB": "2010s",
		"optionC": "1980s",
		"optionD": "2000s",
		"correctANS": "2000s"
		},
	{
		"question": "In the 2010s which was the most popular artist?",
		"optionA": "Regard",
		"optionB": "Topic & A7S",
		"optionC": "Trevor Daniel",
		"optionD": "Ed Sheeran",
		"correctANS": "Topic & A7S"
		},
	{
		"question": "Which of the following genres belongs to Sum 41?",
		"optionA": "Pop",
		"optionB": "Punk",
		"optionC": "Rock",
		"optionD": "Metal",
		"correctANS": "Punk"
		},
	{
		"question": "What is the most popular song of all time?",
		"optionA": "DAKITI",
		"optionB": "Whoopty",
		"optionC": "drivers license",
		"optionD": "WHITOUT YOU",
		"correctANS": "drivers license"
		},
	{
		"question": "In which year Ed Sheeran released the most songs?",
		"optionA": "2017",
		"optionB": "2011",
		"optionC": "2014",
		"optionD": "2019",
		"correctANS": "2017"
		},
	{
		"question": "Which artist was the most popular in 1975?",
		"optionA": "Pink Floyd",
		"optionB": "Francesco De Gregori",
		"optionC": "Mike Oldfield",
		"optionD": "Hot Chocolate",
		"correctANS": "Hot Chocolate"
		},
	{
		"question": "Which of the following genres belongs to Eminem?",
		"optionA": "Pop",
		"optionB": "Rap",
		"optionC": "Rock",
		"optionD": "Urban contemporary",
		"correctANS": "Rap"
		},
	{
		"question": "Who is the most popular pop artist?",
		"optionA": "Tones And I",
		"optionB": "Calum Scott",
		"optionC": "Sam Fischer",
		"optionD": "Alexander 23",
		"correctANS": "Tones And I"
		},
	{
		"question": "What is the most popular genre ever?",
		"optionA": "Irish pop",
		"optionB": "Afroswing",
		"optionC": "Chinese eletropop",
		"optionD": "Estonian pop",
		"correctANS": "Chinese eletropop"
		}
	]
}
